SHAWNA MISCHENKO

Everett, WA (425)760-8340 Shawnakay7@yahoo.com

Account Director for a National Facilities Management Team that provides fully integrated facilities management to support businesses. I have over 18 years of customer service experience, 13 years in management, 5 years in a call center. I am a self motivated leader who strives for excellence in all aspects of my business.

EXPERIENCE

NOVEMBER 2017 - CURRENT ACCOUNT DIRECTOR, COAST WORKPLACE SOLUTIONS

- Senior Facilities Coordinator, promoted to Account Manager after four months employment and Account Director in April 2019
- Manage a portfolio of 10-15 client accounts and directly manage two Senior Account Managers
- Responsible for service delivery on on-demand requests, preventative maintenance and projects, customer relationship interactions and developing supplier network
- Proficient in CorrigoPro, Corrigo Enterprise, Service Channel and SMS Assist work order platforms – including CorrigoPro and SMS Assist Apps
- Allocate and delegate responsibilities amongst my team
- Escalation resolution
- New client ambassador

MAY 2017 - OCTOBER 2017

SCHEDULER/ACCOUNT MANAGER, CLEAN CRAWLS

- Schedule pest control technicians on residential and commercial dispatch requests on demand and recurring
- Pest Solutions customer support and account management
- Proficient in Pestpac software

MARCH 2008 - MARCH 2011

INTER-FUNCTIONAL HELPDESK, FRONTIER COMMUNICATIONS

- Supervisor position handling escalations for the West Coast Region, including BBB and Executive level complaints
- Providing informational support to Consumer Sales Consultants
- Received multiple awards and commendations for excellent customer service

MARCH 2006 - MARCH 2008

CONSUMER SALES CONSULTANT, FRONTIER COMMUNICATIONS

- Promote customer satisfaction and revenue growth through customer service and sales
- Process transactions for new service, move and change orders, in addition to billing adjustments, general inquiries and resolving customer concerns
- Received multiple awards and commendations for excellent customer service

JUNE 2003 – FEBRUARY 2006 RETAIL STORE MANAGER, PAPYRUS

- Responsible for the day-to-day operations (or management) of a high volume retail store, including 10-25 employees
- Custom printing specialist

SKILLS

- Excellent communication
- Ambitious
- Team building and motivation

- Efficient
- Leadership driven
- Accountable

EDUCATION

1999-2003

UNIVERSITY OF WASHINGTON

• Bachelor of Arts – BA, Cultural Anthopology